Rufaida Jumaa



Rufaida Jumaa

Address: Frødalen 24 1sal tv, 3400 Hillerød



+45 20710141



E-mail



GitHub



LinkedIn



Online portfolio

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

JavaScript(ES6)

NodeJS

MySQL

React

Git

Sitecore

Umbraco

Danish driving license

LANGUAGES

Arabic (Mother tongue)

Danish (Fluent for daily use level)

English (Professional level)

French (Basic understanding)

PROFILE

I am an ambitious and curious person with a great passion for Web Development. Since I moved to Denmark, back in 2017, I have learned 2 languages, English and Danish, studied Web Development intensively and joined Kruso as a web developer. I have had a break in my career because I became a mother for the second time. I am now ready to embrace a career as a Web Developer where I can use my WebDevelopment skills from the HackYourFuture Full Stack course together with my background in Information Technology Engineering.

WORK EXPERIENCE

12/2020 - Current ASOSIO- Copenhagen/ Denmark

Web Developer internship working with backend & frontend development tasks working mainly with React.JS(Next.js).

04/2020 - 10/2020 HackYourFutue - Copenhagen/ Denmark

- . Web Developer internship refresh my skills with JavaScript, Node.js,DB and React.
- . I did an Online Course React (Scrimba) Refresh React skills and learn React hooks.
- . Designed and developed Arabi Food restaurant website with a colleague using React.
- . Created my online portfolio using React.

09/2018 - 11/2018 KRUSO A/S - Copenhagen/ Denmark

Frontend Developer working mainly with Umbraco, Sitecore, HTML, CSS, JavaScript. 02/2018 - 08/2018 KRUSO A/S - Copenhagen/ Denmark

Web Developer internship working with backend & frontend development tasks within different departments of the company.

EDUCATION

05/2017 - 14/1/2018 - HackYourFuture - Copenhagen/ Denmark

Full Stack Web Development bootcamp, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, MySQL, Express, React, GIT.

09/2011 - 11/2016 - DAMASCUS UNIVERSITY - Damascus/ Syria

Bachelor of Information Technology Engineering - Computer Systems and Networks 5 year education, Received Bachelor of Science, GPA (73.64) (Equivalent to the Danish "professions-bachelor som diplomingeniør - IT")

2010 - 08/2011 - SYRIAN MINISTRY OF EDUCATION - Damascus/ Syria

General Certificate Of Secondary Education (Scientific Section)

Focus on Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry and Natural Sciences, Arabic, English and French, GPA (95.83).

VOLUNTEER WORK

- . I recently joined Matar Project to give the blind the opportunity to learn and study.
- . I have joined HackYourFuture community again to give back, I support the open office, mentoring in git classes, helping with feedback for application process and interviewing applicants and to give feedback for homework.
- .Teacher / tutor children 6-13 years old Private Mathematics, physics, IT, biology, Arabic, Chemistry.

